Guide to the Mary Seaman Collection of Arlington Mills Photographs 1946
Mary Seaman Collection of Arlington Mills Photographs
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Mary Seaman Collection of Arlington Mills Photographs, 1946
6771 P
Mary Seaman; Arlington Mills
1 file folder
Gelatin silver print, photographs.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Photographs of the 1946 Christmas Party at Arlington Mills in Lawrence, Massachusetts.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Inccludes en snapshots of a Christmas Party at Arlington Mills, in Lawrence, Massachusetts. This party most likely took place in 1946. Pictured are groups of employees, Santa Claus, Christmas decorations, and mill machinery.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Santa Claus; Arlington Mills.
Subjects:
Christmas party; Employees; Spinning machinery; Textile machinery; Textile workers
Geographic Subjects:
Lawrence (Mass.)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Related Collections:
6517: Arlington Mills Records
6517 G: Arlington Mills Graphics
6517 GPN: Arlington Mills Glass Plate Negatives
6517 P: Arlington Mills Photographs
6517 PUBS: Arlington Mills Publications
CONTAINER LIST
- Christmas Party Snapshots, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Female employees at Christmas party, 1946; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Female employees at Christmas party, Arlington Mills, Lawrence, Mass. Gelatin silver print snapshot. Image depicts several female employees of the Arlington Mills (Mill 28) in Lawrence, Mass., at a Christmas party, probably in 1946. They are sitting at a table on which are several bottles of wine or champagne (?). "Merry Xmas" sign on pole in background. 9 x 9 cm.
    Format: black and white photograph.
  - Item 2: Employees with Santa Claus at Christmas party, 1946; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Employees with Santa Claus at Christmas party, Arlington Mills, Lawrence, Mass. Gelatin silver print snapshot. Image depicts several employees of the Arlington Mills (Mill 28) in Lawrence, Mass., seated at a table with Santa Claus in the background at a Christmas party, probably in 1946. 9 x 9 cm.
  - Item 3: Employees with Santa Claus at Christmas party, 1946; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Employees with Santa Claus at Christmas party, Arlington Mills, Lawrence, Mass. Gelatin silver print snapshot. Image depicts several employees of the Arlington Mills (Mill 28) in Lawrence, Mass., in a group portrait with Santa Claus seated in the center. Tinsel hangs between poles in the background; Christmas party, probably in 1946. 9 x 9 cm.
  - Item 4: Female employees at Christmas party, 1946; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Female employees at Christmas party, Arlington Mills, Lawrence, Mass. Gelatin silver print snapshot. Image depicts a group of female employees posed together at a Christmas party, probably in 1946, in the Arlington Mills (Mill 28) in Lawrence, Mass. One woman holds a 'Merry Xmas" sign; two others hold a partially obscured sign that reads, in part, "Holiday.." 9 x 9 cm.
  - Item 5: Male employee with Santa Claus at Christmas party, 1946; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Male employee with Santa Claus at Christmas party, Arlington Mills, Lawrence, Mass. Gelatin silver print snapshot. Image depicts a male employee of the Arlington Mills (Mill 28) in Lawrence, Mass., with Santa Claus at a Christmas party, probably in 1946. Tinsel hangs in the background. 9 x 9 cm.
  - Item 6: Female employees at table at Christmas party, 1946; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Female employees at table at Christmas party, Arlington Mills, Lawrence, Mass. Gelatin silver print snapshot. Image depicts several female employees of the Arlington Mills (Mill 28) in Lawrence, Mass., at a table at a Christmas party, probably in 1946. The table is loaded with plates of food and cups. 9 x 9 cm.
  - Item 7: Christmas party, spinning room, 1946; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Christmas party, spinning room, Arlington Mills, Lawrence, Mass. Gelatin silver print snapshot. Image depicts a table in the spinning room of the Arlington Mills (Mill 28) in Lawrence, Mass., at a Christmas party, probably in 1946. Several female employees are sitting at the table; one male and two female employees stand behind it. Creels and spinning machinery visible in background. 9 x 9 cm.
  - Item 8: Santa Claus at Christmas party, 1946; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Santa Claus at Christmas party, Arlington Mills, Lawrence, Mass. Gelatin silver print snapshot. Image depicts Santa Claus at a Christmas party in the Arlington Mills (Mill 28) in Lawrence, Mass., probably in 1946. The backs of several employees are visible on the right. tinsel is strung between two poles. 9 x 9 cm.
  - Item 9: Santa Claus with male employee at Christmas party, 1946; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Santa Claus with male employee at Christmas party, Arlington Mills, Lawrence, Mass. Gelatin silver print snapshot. Image depicts Santa Claus seated on the knee of a male employee at a Christmas party in the Arlington Mills (Mill 28) in Lawrence, Mass., probably in 1946. Creels and spinning machinery visible in background. 9 x 9 cm.
  - Item 10: Female employees at Christmas party, 1946; black and white photograph (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Female employees at Christmas party, Arlington Mills, Lawrence, Mass. Gelatin silver print snapshot. Image depicts a group of female employees posed together at a Christmas party in the Arlington Mills (Mill 28) in Lawrence, Mass., probably in 1946. 9 x 9 cm.